Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-2013 and undated; 6
  - Paramount Poultry 5--Pearl Bailey, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-054)
    Washing; 6 Chickens; Stuffing; Recipe Book; Turkey
  - Paramount Poultry 7--5 spots, Undated (Box AV42, Film-reel RL11500-F16-055)
  - Paramount Poultry 7--5 spots, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-056)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 8--Anti-Smoking 6:00, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-057)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 14--Women and Smoking, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-058)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 15--Automatic Cigarette, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-059)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 17, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-060)
    Man Smoking in Reverse; Cigarette Smoking
  - U.S. Public Health Service 18--American Cancer Society, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-061)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 19, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-062)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 20, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-063)
    Two Girls; Cigarette in Ashtray
  - U.S. Public Health Service 21--Presentation reel, Women and Smoking, 1977 (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-064)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 22--Anti-Smoking 6:00, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-065)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 23, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-066)
    Fitzgerald; Logia; Spielbergs
  - U.S. Public Health Service 24, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-067)
    Quit Now; Barbara Spielberg; Zohra
  - 635--Composite reel, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-068)
  - ILGWU 33--Mention in Harper Valley, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-069)
  - New York Times 18--Commercials, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-070)
  - Paramount Poultry 3, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-071)
  - Paramount Poultry 4, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-072)
    Washing; 6 Chickens; Stuffing
  - Paramount Poultry 6, 1976 (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F16-073)
    Mamma Hen; Leftovers; Pots; Joy; Success Story
  - Composite reel 2, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-074)
    Puppy Palace; U.S. Public Health Service; Lee's Carpet; Burlington; Life Cereal; American Cancer Society
  - ILGWU--Report to Convention, 1983 (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-075)
  - Lever Brothers--Hero detergent, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-076)
  - ILGWU 24--Commercials and parodies, 1977 (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-077)
  - New York Times 8--24 spots, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-078)
  - New York Times 9, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-079)
  - New York Times 10--10 spots, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-080)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 9, Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-081)
    Women Smoking; That's a Good Reason; Just Like Men; What Do I Tell Myself Now
  - U.S. Public Health Service 10--17 commercials (English and Spanish), Undated (Box AV44, Film-reel RL11500-F16-082)
  - New York Times 11, Undated (Box AV45, Film-reel RL11500-F16-083)
  - New York Times 21, Undated (Box AV45, Film-reel RL11500-F16-084)
  - ILGWU--Report to Convention, 1980 (Box AV45, Film-reel RL11500-F16-085)
  - Composite reel 3--New York Times and U.S. Public Health Service, Undated (Box AV45, Film-reel RL11500-F16-086)
  - New York Times--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F35-001)
  - New York Times--Op Ed, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F35-002)
  - New York Times 13--Bob Loggia, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F35-003)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 16--Automatic Cigarette, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F35-004)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 20, Undated (Box AV43, Film-reel RL11500-F35-005)
  - Goya reel 1, takes 1-100, 1985 (Box AV42, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-001)
  - Goya reel 2, takes 101-199, 1985 (Box AV42, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-002)
  - ILGWU Round-up presentation, "20 Years of Look for the Union Label", 1995 (Box AV42, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-003)
  - ILGWU Round-up presentation, "20 Years of Look for the Union Label", 1995 (Box AV44, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-004)
  - ILGWU--Sweatshop, Undated (Box AV44, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-005)
  - Party of Karen's Closing Ceremony, Undated (Box AV44, Video-cassette RL11500-BCAM-006)
  - Paula Green compilation reel, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-001)
  - Paula Green from 16mm film, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-002)
  - Paula Green inverview with Clive Challis, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-003)
  - Paula Green inverviewed by Tamee Gunnell, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-004)
  - Paula Green One Club Creative Hall of Fame Introduction, 2012 (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-005)
  - Paula Green One Club Creative Hall of Fame Introduction and speech, 2012 (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-006)
  - Paula Green's radio music, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-007)
    New York Times: Home Delivery; Composite jingles; Subaru radio spots
  - The Real Mad Men & Women of Madison Avenue (WNET), 2013 (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-008)
  - The Reel Paula Green, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-009)
    Compilation: New York Times; Paramount Poultry; Goya Foods; Marval Poultry; Standard Milling; Sterling Bank; American Cancer Society; ILGWU
  - The Reel Paula Green, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-010)
  - Paula Green: ILGWU and parodies, Undated (Box AV44, Video-disc RL11500-OP-011)
  - ILGWU--Health Care, Undated (Box AV44, Audio-cassette RL11500-DAT-001)
  - Avis Rent-a-Car Demo, 1963 (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-001)
    Doyle Dane Bernbach.
  - Burlington vocal final, 1966 (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-002)
    Doyle Dane Bernbach. "Getting Rid of the Work Is the Work of Burlington."
  - Goodman's Noodle Soup--Noodl-y, 1962 (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-003)
  - Lawry's Spaghetti Sauce, 1959 (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-004)
  - Pelican Music 63-198, Undated (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-005)
  - Tee Vee Toons: The Commercials. TVT Records, 1989 (Box AV46, Audio-phonodisc RL11500-PD-006)
  - Unnumbered duplicates, various formats (Box AV47)